<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:image="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-image/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/</loc>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-tedx-speaking-1.png</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi delivering keynote presentation at TEDx event - youth advocate and public speaker on stage with microphone</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi TEDx Speaker - Youth Advocate and Changemaker</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-tedx-speaking-2.jpeg</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi speaking at TEDxMcFarren conference - youth advocate presenting on leadership and innovation to audience</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi TEDxMcFarren Speaker - Leadership and Innovation Presentation</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-formal-headshot.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi professional headshot - youth advocate, public speaker, and founder of Dr. Interested organization</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi Professional Photo - Youth Advocate and Public Speaker</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-camera-photographer.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi with professional camera equipment - photographer and content creator documenting youth advocacy work</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi Photographer - Youth Advocate and Content Creator</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-dr-interested-founder.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi as founder of Dr. Interested organization - youth mentorship and advocacy program leader</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi Dr. Interested Founder - Youth Mentorship Program</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-informal-portrait.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi casual portrait - approachable youth advocate and community leader</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi Casual Photo - Youth Advocate and Community Leader</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-lab-coat-medical-research.JPG</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi in laboratory setting wearing lab coat - STEM education advocate and medical research volunteer</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi Medical Research - STEM Education and Healthcare Advocacy</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-tennis-sports.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi playing tennis - athlete promoting Play-to-Heal movement for youth mental health through sports</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi Tennis Player - Play-to-Heal Movement Advocate</image:title>
    </image:image>
    <image:image>
  <image:loc>https://adilmukhi.vercel.app/pictures/adil-mukhi-graduation.jpg</image:loc>
      <image:caption>Adil Mukhi graduation photo at Valleys - academic achievement and educational milestone</image:caption>
      <image:title>Adil Mukhi Graduation - Academic Achievement and Educational Excellence</image:title>
    </image:image>
  </url>
</urlset>
